(Penny:)Yeah, okay.
The thing is, I kind of
(Penny:)told my father
we got back together again.
(Leonard:)What? Why?
(Penny:)Well, you're the first guy
(Penny:)he's ever really approved of,
you know?
(Penny:)You're a scientist
who went to college
(Penny:)and you don't have a neck tattoo
(Penny:)or outstanding warrants
or... or a baby.
(Leonard:)What kind of guys
did you used to go out with?
(Penny:)Just guys.
(Penny:)Anyway, when I told him
we split up, he was heartbroken,
and he kept bugging me:
"How's Leonard?
"Why can't you get
back together with Leonard?
(Penny:)I bet Leonard never
tipped a cow over on himself."
(Penny:)So to get him off my back,
(Penny:)I told him
we worked things out.
(Leonard:)Really?
How-how'd we manage that?
(Leonard:)What?
I mean, did you apologize?
(Leonard:)Did you have to woo me?
(Penny:)Get over yourself.
(Penny:)I whistled, you came running.
(Leonard:)Yeah, no, I don't think so.
(Penny:)Okay, why are you
arguing about this?
(Leonard:)I'm just saying,
(Leonard:)if we fake got back together,